{
"question": "海",
"answer": "うみ"
},
{
"question": "授業",
"answer": "じゅぎょう"
},
{
"question": "銀行",
"answer": "ぎんこう"
},
{
"question": "写真",
"answer": "しゃしん"
},
{
"question": "冬",
"answer": "ふゆ"
},
{
"question": "村",
"answer": "むら"
},
{
"question": "傘",
"answer": "かさ"
},
{
"question": "口",
"answer": "くち"
},
{
"question": "橋",
"answer": "はし"
},
{
"question": "病院",
"answer": "びょういん"
},
{
"question": "図書館",
"answer": "としょかん"
},
{
"question": "春",
"answer": "はる"
},
{
"question": "買い物",
"answer": "かいもの"
},
{
"question": "椅子",
"answer": "いす"
},
{
"question": "自動車",
"answer": "じどうしゃ"
},
{
"question": "色",
"answer": "いろ"
},
{
"question": "卵",
"answer": "たまご"
},
{
"question": "肉",
"answer": "にく"
},
{
"question": "風邪",
"answer": "かぜ"
},
{
"question": "掃除",
"answer": "そうじ"
},
